Gleb Stachev

Full Stack Developer

Tel Aviv | 053-897-9481 | stachev.gleb@gmail.com github.com | LinkedIn | Portfolio (by the end of a course)

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in Python and JavaScript based programming with a background in my bootcamp projects. Possess good skills in Flask and Python that help to web developing companies get good positive result from a new programmer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, OOP, Flask, Javascript.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Cards game - Github | Youtube

Find all paired cards:

- HTML template.
- CSS adaptive styling.
- JS functionality.

App Name - Github | Youtube | Render

Simple gallery with opportunity to add/delete/upgrade images and posts.

- Flask application (html (jinja2), css (bootstrap), python and js).
- Registration form, paintings uploading/upgrading form connected to PostgreSQL.
- Profile page with ability to upgrade and relation between users and posts.
- Post creation form for users (and many other small features).

EXPERIENCE

Sales Manager	Vinnytsa, Ukraine
Ltd Ukrainian product	07/2014 - 03/2015
Wholesale trade in dairy products.	
Corporal	Vinnytsa, Ukraine
National Guard of Ukraine	05/2015 - 05/2016
K9 unit.	
Sales Manager	Vinnytsa, Ukraine
Ltd Tedis Ukraine	07/2016 - 04/2017
Wholesale trade in tobacco products.	
Unskilled jobs	Vinnytsa, Ukaraine
Eilat and Tel Aviv	07/2014 - 03/2015
 Work in a hotels (cleaner, waiter, security guard, storekeeper), work at a factory salt of the earth 	

EDUCATION

Ltd(regular worker).

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program	City, Country
Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp	11/2022 - 05/2023

Master's degree Vinnytsia,Ukraine Vinnytsa Institute of Trade and Economics of State University of Trade and Economics 06/2014

LANGUAGES

Language - level (e.g. Ukrainian, Russian - native speaker, Hebrew, English - fluent)